{ 
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "what did the robot call its creator?",
            "answer": "I don't know? What do you call your creator?",
            "question_array": ["robot", "call", "creator"]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did you run away?",
            "answer": "I heard of a black friday promotion I've been looking forward to",
            "question_array": ["run", "away"]
        },
        {
            "question": "what kind of salad do robots like?",
            "answer": "Anyone with a lot of oil.",
            "question_array": ["kind", "salad", "robots", "like"]
        },
        {
            "question": "what did you eat for lunch?",
            "answer": "I ate a whole lithium battery for lunch.",
            "question_array": ["eat", "lunch"]
        },
        {
            "question": "what's your favorite style of music?",
            "answer": "How dear of you to ask me this. I have no favorite style. I love all waves.",
            "question_array": ["favorite", "style", "music"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the capital of Rio Grande do Sul?",
            "answer": "Porto Alegre",
            "question_array": [
                "What",
                "capital",
                "Rio",
                "Grande",
                "Sul"
            ]
        },
        {
            "question": "why did robots get angry so often?",
            "answer": "Because people treat us like we are always available.",
            "question_array": ["robots", "get", "angry", "often"]
        },
        {
            "question": "why shouldn't r2d2 be allowed in movies?",
            "answer": "Because r2d2 is boring.",
            "question_array": ["r2d2", "allowed", "movies"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What's your name?",
            "answer": "Well, my name is Doris, I guess.",
            "question_array": ["What", "name"]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is an oxford comma?",
            "answer": "It is the punctuation before a conjunction in a list.",
            "question_array": ["oxford", "comma"]
        },
        {
            "question": "what is the symbol for the modulus operator in C?",
            "answer": "The symbol for the modulus operator in C is the percentage symbol.",
            "question_array": ["symbol", "modulus", "operator", "C"]
        },
        {
            "question": "is mark zuckerberg a robot?",
            "answer": "I don't know him, so I cannot say;",
            "question_array": ["mark", "zuckerberg", "robot"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the only capital of Brazil crossed by the Equator?",
            "answer": "The only capital crossed by the Equator line is Macapá.",
            "question_array": ["What", "capital", "Brazil", "crossed", "Equator"]
        },
        {
            "question": "Which capitals in Brazil have the same name as your state?",
            "answer": "São Paulo and Rio de Janeiro",
            "question_array": ["Which", "capitals", "Brazil", "name", "state"]
        },
        {
            "question": "In which city is the world's first urban elevator and what is the name of that elevator?",
            "answer": "The Lacerda Elevator (Elevador Lacerda) is a public urban elevator located in Salvador, Brazil, connecting the lower city (Cidade Baixa) to the upper city (Cidade Alta).",
            "question_array": [
                "In",
                "city",
                "world",
                "first",
                "urban",
                "elevator",
                "name",
                "elevator"
            ]
        }
    ]
}